<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Get Started on LinkedPipes Applications Docs</title>
    <link>https://docs.applications.linkedpipes.com/get-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Get Started on LinkedPipes Applications Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://docs.applications.linkedpipes.com/get-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1. About</title>
      <link>https://docs.applications.linkedpipes.com/get-started/1.what_is/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.applications.linkedpipes.com/get-started/1.what_is/</guid>
      <description>LinkedPipes Applications is a visualization web platform that allows the users to explore, visualize and publish LinkedData based visualizer applications. Applications created with these platforms can be easily published and integrated anywhere on the Web!
The main features of the platform can be described as follows:
 The user owns and manages his private data space. He can upload graph data therefrom his computer or provide an URL from which the data should be imported.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. Installation</title>
      <link>https://docs.applications.linkedpipes.com/get-started/2.installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.applications.linkedpipes.com/get-started/2.installation/</guid>
      <description>⚙️ Prerequisites Make sure to have the following installed in your OS:
 Git  Docker  Docker-compose   🚀 Quick start If you do not consider yourself a developer who is working, contributing or tweaking your own instance of the platform, the fastest way to access the platform would be to simply navigate to the latest instance available at applications.linkedpipes.com.
If you do, the consequite sections will guide you through all possible installation scenarious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. Core concepts</title>
      <link>https://docs.applications.linkedpipes.com/get-started/3.core-concepts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.applications.linkedpipes.com/get-started/3.core-concepts/</guid>
      <description>The following section will introduce the main concepts and terms used within platform.
LinkedPipes Applications consist of multiple services encorporated into docker containers, interacting within docker-compose environment. As a part of [LinkedPipes] suite, we are relying on two extra software services that are responsible for discovering, retreiving and transforming your LinkedData sources to be visualized. It is recommended to get yourself familiar with conceptual description of those services, since it provides a better understanding on what exactly is happening during Data Preparation workflow process.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>